{
    "subject": "resource/Meggitt",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Dorset",
    "human_readable": "Meggitt is located in Dorset.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.907970130443573,
            "question": "What is the history of Meggitt in Dorset?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8766695261001587,
            "question": "Where is Meggitt located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6643255352973938,
            "question": "What county is Meggitt in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6170412302017212,
            "question": "Is Meggitt a town or a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4789724051952362,
            "question": "In what region of England is Meggitt situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32519370317459106,
            "question": "What type of company is Meggitt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26735565066337585,
            "question": "Is Meggitt a publicly traded company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2596535384654999,
            "question": "What industries does Meggitt operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18769395351409912,
            "question": "Does Meggitt have any subsidiaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17921923100948334,
            "question": "Does Meggitt manufacture any products?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Meggitt is located in Dorset.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2910_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Meggitt have any subsidiaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2910_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industries does Meggitt operate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2910_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Meggitt a publicly traded company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2910_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2910_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Meggitt is located in Dorset\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nWhile it is true that Meggitt has a location mentioned in one of the documents as being \"head-quartered\" in Dorset, at Bournemouth Airport (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2910/re-ranker-msmarco/138.txt), this is not an exhaustive or definitive statement about Meggitt's location. In fact, another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2910/re-ranker-msmarco/141.txt) mentions that Meggitt's headquarters moved from Bournemouth Airport to Coventry in 2020, which suggests that the location of interest may not be accurate. Therefore, based on these documents alone, we cannot conclude with certainty that Meggitt is indeed located in Dorset."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Meggitt is located in Dorset.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention that Meggitt is headquartered at Bournemouth Airport, which is located in Dorset, United Kingdom."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Although Meggitt has its headquarters in Dorset, the company was relocated to Coventry in 2020 as mentioned in context #5.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state Meggitt's headquarters moved from Bournemouth Airport to Coventry in 2020.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Meggitt's headquarters moved from Bournemouth Airport to Coventry in 2020, as stated in the context information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}